Contact

tezakemp40@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alteza-kemp-643658112 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Medical-Surgical Registered Nurses

Alteza Kemp

Registered Nurse at HealthTrust Workforce Solutions Saint Petersburg, Florida

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Medical-Surgical, Telemetry and Inpatient Rehab with experience in Stroke, Brain Injury and Spinal Cord Injury. A professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Ohio University. Currently licensed in Florida!

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions Registered Nurse May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months) Saint Petersburg, Florida

Florida Hospital Tampa Registered Nurse March 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months) Tampa, Florida

Manatee Memorial Hospital Registered Nurse March 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months) Bradenton, Florida

TravelMax
Travrl Nurse
June 2017 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Working currently on different units including Inpatient Rehab, Med-Surg Oncology, Ortho and PCU.

Ohio Health Rehabilitation Hospital Nurse Manager September 2013 - Present (6 years 11 months) Columbus. Ohio Area I started here as a travel nurse and then came on permanently. I worked on the floor as a staff nurse and started doing charge nurse after some time on the unit. I then applied for the nurse manger position.

Medical Center of Newark Registered Nurse October 2010 - December 2012 (2 years 3 months) Newark, Oh

Med-Surg

Education

Ohio University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2013 - 2015)